SANISH BASUKALA

FULL STACK DEVELOPER



🔀 sanishbasukala1@gmail.com, 🔮 Kathmandu, Nepal



+977 9863447422



SanishBasukala



in sanish basukala



TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Programming Language: C#, JavaScript/TypeScript
- Web Development: HTML, CSS, ASP.NET, React, JQuery, Angular
- Database Management: SQL Server (SSMS), T-SQL
- Version Control: Git, SVN

SOFT SKILLS

- Adaptability
- Problem-solving
- Teamwork
- Communication
- Time Management
- Critical Thinking

HONORS & AWARDS

- First Class Honors in Bsc. (Hons) Computing
- AAA Scholarship in Computing

EDUCATION

- **Bsc. Hons Computing** 2021 2023 **Islington College**
- +2 Science 2018 - 2020 **GIHE**

INTERESTS

Web development, UX Design

Professional Summary

Full-stack developer with 2+ years of experience in building scalable web applications using C#, ASP.NET, Angular, and SQL Server. Delivered complex healthcare projects like operation theater management and commission tracking systems, enhancing efficiency and user experience.

Work Experience

Full Stack Developer

Aug 2023 - Present

DTRG Network

- Developed multiple features for the existing multi-tenant system according to user requirement.
- Optimized SQL queries, improving overall application performance by 60%.
- · Redesigned UX of pages, significantly improving client satisfaction and increasing user engagement by 20%.

Front End Developer

Jul 2022 - Nov 2022

PL Multimedia Services Pvt. Ltd.

- Designed webpages and wireframes using Figma.
- Developed a fully functional user interface for the web application.

Projects

Doctor Commission Setup

Mar 2024 - Jul 2024

- Developed a system to map commission to doctors based on their roles (consultant, performer, referrer).
- · Implemented reporting features to track commissions and earnings of doctors based on patient bills.

Operation Theater Management System

Jan 2023 - Mar 2024

- · Designed and implemented booking, scheduling, and rescheduling functionalities for OT appointments.
- · Created algorithms for revenue distribution based on surgery roles, time allocation, and contractual agreements.

Dental Clinic Management System

Nov 2023 - Jan 2024

- Implemented a user-friendly interface for dental professionals to create and manage patient treatment plans, history, diagnosis and medication.
- Enabled users to upload and associate medical images within the system.